Yerassilova Gaukhar

29 years old

+7 (775) 9994224 gaumus.work@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://muse775.github.io/GY_portfolio/

I am a beginner web developer with basic knowledge of HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript. Previously I've been working in the oil and gas sector for more than 5 years, mainly in administrative positions. At the moment I am changing my professional sphere since I find myself being fascinated by web development and programming. I suppose that programming is a great platform to fully realize my potential and apply personal, analytical skills and advanced knowledge of foreign languages to become a better professional.

Current goals:

- To work as part of a team;
- To improve my knowledge and competence in web development;
- To become a professional front-end developer.

Key Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, VueJS, SASS/SCSS, Gulp/Webpack, Photoshop, Figma

Education and professional development

2020 Johns Hopkins University

Coursera.org, HTML, CSS, and Javascript for Web Developers

2020 University of Michigan

Coursera.org, Interactivity with JavaScript

2020 Arizona State University

Coursera.org, Business English: Management and Leadership

2011 Kazakh State University of International Relations and World Languages

Almaty, Oriental studies

Work experience

2015-2019 KazInRuss-trading LLP

Almaty

Business Assistant to General Manager

2012-2015 Independent translation Agencies

Almaty/Astana

Freelance translator

2011-2013 KazTransOil JSC

Astana

Assistant of Deputy General Director for Business Support

2007-2008 Ordamed Central Asia Inc.

Almaty

Interpreter

Languages

Russian — Native

Kazakh — Native

English — Fluent

Japanese — Intermediate

Spanish — Elementary